module.exports = [
    {
        topic: "Work and Studies ",
        questions: [
            { question: "1. Do you work or are you a student?", answer: "1. I've been working as an English teacher for about 15 years now, and for the last 10 years I've specialized exclusively in teaching IELTS. And I absolutely love what I do. Of course, sometimes I feel tired and emotionally drained, especially when I have to mark my students' essays until midnight, but I just don't see myself doing anything other than teaching.\n\n2. It's been a few years now since I started working full time. I work in Experiential Marketing and I absolutely love it because it's the type of job that really lets you utilize all of your talents. One day you can be making a budget, and the next day you can be learning to use a drill because you need to drill holes in the floor. It's very versatile. It's for people who don't want to be the same as the day before.\n\n3. Currently, I am in my senior year of high school. And I am graduating this year. Now I am working hard in order to get passing grades because l am planning to study abroad. I want to major in Journalism bacause I have always had a strong passion for writing, and I do not see myself doing anything else. And there is a great two-year diploma Journalism program at Seneca college in Canada. So if everything is ok, 9 months from now I will be studying there. And hopefully not online.\n\n4. I neither work nor study. At the moment I have a Bachelor's degree, and I'm planning to apply for a Master's degree as soon as I meet the requirements of the program. It seems I've missed the boat for the fall semester, so I'll try not to miss the deadline for applying for the winter one.\n\n5. Neither. Having worked for many years in the field of Advertising, I made a decision to make a career change and now that I have completed a program, I want to pursue a career in IT.\n\n6. Currently I'm unemployed. Half a year ago the company I had been working at for many years started massive layoffs. One day I was made redundant among others. Unfortunately, I'm still looking for a job which would be in line with my qualifications and experience, but it's not an easy task." },
            { question: "2. What work do you do? / What subjects are you studying?", answer: "1. I work as a software developer. I create and fix computer programs, and I work with others to come up with new ideas. I like solving problems in my job.\n\n2. I'm a marketing manager. I make plans to sell products, look at what people like to buy, and manage social media pages. My job is interesting because I get to be creative.\n\n3. I work as a nurse in a hospital. I take care of patients, give them medicine, and help doctors. It’s a very rewarding job because I get to help people.\n\n4. I am studying computer science at university. I learn about coding, how to organize data, and artificial intelligence. These topics are really interesting to me because they are about new technology.\n\n5. I am studying business administration. My classes include marketing, finance, management, and how to start a business. This knowledge will help me in my future career.\n\n6. I study environmental science. My subjects are about nature, how to protect the environment, and sustainable living. I care about this field because it deals with important issues for our planet." },
            { question: "3. Why did you choose that job?", answer: "1. I chose this job because I have always been interested in technology. As a child, I loved playing with computers and figuring out how they work. Becoming a software developer seemed like the perfect way to turn my hobby into a career\n\n2. I decided to become a marketing manager because I enjoy being creative and working with people. Marketing allows me to use my creativity to come up with new ideas and strategies, and I like the challenge of understanding what customers want.\n\n3. I chose nursing because I wanted to do something meaningful that helps people. I have always been compassionate and wanted a job where I could make a difference in someone’s life. Nursing is perfect for that." },
            { question: "4. Why did you choose to study that subject?", answer: "1. I chose computer science because I've always been fascinated by computers and technology. I enjoyed programming and understanding how different software works. Turning my passion into a career and learning about cutting-edge technologies motivated me to pursue this field.\n\n2. I decided to study business administration because I enjoy working with people and developing new ideas. Marketing, finance, and management intrigued me because they provide insights into how businesses operate and how they can be improved.\n\n3. I opted for environmental science because I'm passionate about nature conservation. I've always cared deeply about the environment and wanted to understand more about ecology, sustainable practices, and how we can protect our planet for future generations." },
            { question: "5. Do you like your job?", answer: "1. Yes, I really like my job. I enjoy the creativity it allows and the opportunity to solve interesting problems. Every day, I feel like I'm doing something meaningful.\n\n2. Absolutely, I find my job fulfilling. I appreciate the chance to work in a team and interact with different people, which helps me grow professionally.\n\n3. Overall, yes, I am satisfied with my job. It provides me with a stable income and allows me to achieve both personal and professional goals." },
            { question: "6. Is there anything you dislike about your job?", answer: "1. Sometimes, I find the workload overwhelming, especially when there are tight deadlines to meet. Balancing multiple tasks can be challenging.\n\n2. While I enjoy most aspects of my job, there are occasional administrative tasks that I find tedious. They are necessary but not as engaging as the more creative aspects of my work.\n\n3. Occasionally, I encounter communication challenges with team members, which can slow down progress. Clear and effective communication is crucial, and overcoming these hurdles requires patience and effort." },
            { question: "7. What do you like about your studies?", answer: "1. I enjoy the opportunity to learn new concepts and expand my knowledge in my chosen field. Studying allows me to delve deeper into subjects that genuinely interest me and prepares me for future career opportunities.\n\n2. I appreciate the interactions with professors and classmates during discussions and group projects. It's enriching to hear different perspectives and collaborate with others who share similar academic interests.\n\n3. The sense of accomplishment I feel when I understand complex topics or achieve good grades is rewarding. It motivates me to keep pushing myself and strive for academic excellence." },
            { question: "8. What do you dislike about your studies?", answer: "1. One aspect I find challenging is the heavy workload and deadlines for assignments and exams. It can be stressful trying to manage everything effectively.\n\n2. Sometimes, certain subjects or topics are more difficult to grasp, requiring extra time and effort to understand fully. This can be frustrating when trying to keep up with the pace of the curriculum.\n\n3. Occasionally, I find large lecture classes impersonal, making it harder to engage deeply with the material or ask questions. I prefer smaller, more interactive settings where I can interact more directly with the instructor." },
            { question: "9. What was your dream job when you were young?", answer: "1. When I was young, I dreamed of becoming an astronaut. The idea of exploring space and experiencing zero gravity fascinated me beyond measure.\n\n2. My dream job was to be a veterinarian. I've always had a deep love for animals and wanted to help sick and injured pets get better.\n\n3. I wanted to be a professional athlete, particularly in soccer. Playing sports was my passion, and the idea of competing at a high level excited me." },
            { question: "10. Have you changed your mind on your dream job?", answer: "1. Yes, I've changed my mind about my dream job as I grew older and learned more about different career paths. My interests evolved, and I found new passions that aligned better with my skills and values.\n\n2. Over time, I realized the practical challenges and requirements of my childhood dream job didn't match my evolving interests and aspirations. I discovered new fields that excited me more and seemed more realistic.\n\n3. While my childhood dream job was exciting, I've come to appreciate other professions that offer different kinds of fulfillment and align better with my current goals and lifestyle." },
        ]
    },
    {
        topic: "Hometown",
        questions: [
            { question: "1. Please describe your hometown a little.", answer: "1. My hometown is a small coastal town nestled between mountains and the sea. It's known for its picturesque views, sandy beaches, and friendly community atmosphere.\n\n2. I come from a bustling city with diverse neighborhoods, vibrant street markets, and a rich cultural heritage. The cityscape is a blend of modern skyscrapers and historical landmarks.\n\n3. My hometown is a quaint rural village surrounded by lush green fields and rolling hills. Life here is peaceful, with close-knit community gatherings and a focus on traditional agricultural practices." },
            { question: "2. What is your town well-known for?", answer: "1. My town is well-known for its annual festivals that celebrate local culture and traditions. These events attract visitors from all over and showcase our community's vibrant spirit.\n\n2. We are renowned for our historical landmarks, such as ancient temples and architectural marvels, which draw tourists interested in exploring our rich heritage.\n\n3. Our town is famous for its culinary delights, especially our regional dishes and street food. Food enthusiasts often visit to savor the authentic flavors and diverse cuisine." },
            { question: "3. Do you like your hometown?", answer: "1. Yes, I love my hometown. It's a place where I have fond memories of growing up, surrounded by supportive friends and family. The sense of community here is strong, and I appreciate the laid-back lifestyle.\n\n2. Overall, I have mixed feelings about my hometown. While I cherish the familiarity and close-knit community, I also crave the excitement and opportunities that larger cities offer.\n\n3. While there are aspects of my hometown that I appreciate, such as its natural beauty and peaceful atmosphere, I sometimes feel limited by its small size and lack of career prospects." },
            { question: "4. Is that a big city or a small place?", answer: "1. It's a small place, where everyone knows each other and the community is tightly knit. Despite its size, it has a lot of charm and character.\n\n2. It's a big city with a bustling atmosphere and diverse neighborhoods. There's always something happening, and you can find a wide range of activities and cultural events.\n\n3. It's a medium-sized town that strikes a balance between urban conveniences and a more relaxed pace of life. It offers enough amenities without feeling overwhelming." },
            { question: "5. How long have you been living there?", answer: "1. I have been living here all my life. It's where I grew up and where I have many cherished memories.\n\n2. I moved here a few years ago for work/study reasons. It's been an interesting experience adapting to a new environment.\n\n3. I've been living here for about [number of years]. Over time, I've grown attached to the community and feel a strong sense of belonging."},
            { question: "6. Do you think you will continue living there for a long time?", answer: "1. Yes, I see myself staying here for the foreseeable future. It's a place I feel comfortable in, and I have strong ties to the community.\n\n2. No, I think I might eventually move to pursue new opportunities or a different lifestyle. While I appreciate my current hometown, I'm open to exploring other places.\n\n3. It's hard to say at this point. My decision will depend on various factors such as career opportunities, family considerations, and personal preferences." },
            { question: "7. Would you like to live in the countryside in the future?", answer: "1. Yes, I think living in the countryside would be peaceful and refreshing. It would be a nice change from city life, and I appreciate the natural beauty and tranquility.\n\n2. No, I prefer the convenience and amenities of urban living. The countryside is beautiful, but I feel more connected to the energy and opportunities that cities offer.\n\n3. I'm open to the idea. It depends on the specific location and lifestyle. If the countryside offers a good balance of nature and access to essential services, I could see myself enjoying living there." },
            { question: "8. Have you ever lived in the coutryside?", answer: "1. Yes, I have lived in the countryside for a short period of time. It was a peaceful experience surrounded by nature, away from the hustle and bustle of city life.\n\n2. No, I have never lived in the countryside, but I have visited rural areas and enjoyed the tranquility and scenic landscapes.\n\n3. I grew up in the countryside. It was a close-knit community where everyone knew each other, and I have fond memories of exploring nature and enjoying the slower pace of life." },
            { question: "9. Do you ever spend time in the countryside?", answer: "Sorry, no answer found for this question." },
            { question: "10. What is the difference between living in the countryside and the city?", answer: "Sorry, no answer found for this question." },
            { question: "11. What do people living in the countryside like to do?", answer: "Sorry, no answer found for this question." },
            { question: "12. What do you like to do in the countryside?", answer: "Sorry, no answer found for this question." },
            { question: "13. How has your town changed over the last 20 years?", answer: "Sorry, no answer found for this question." },

        ]
    },
];